<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Catania</string>
    <string name="acitrezza">Sea</string>
    <string name="etna">Etna</string>
    <string name="folklore">Saint\'Agata</string>
    <string name="desc_folklore">The feast of St. Agatha is the most important religious festival in the city of Catania. It is celebrated in honor of the patron saint of the city, and is one of the most followed Catholic religious festivals, precisely because of the number of people it involves and attracts. It takes place every year from 3 to 5 February, 12 February and 17 August. The February anniversary is linked to the martyrdom of the saint from Catania, while the date of August recalls the return to Catania of his remains, after they had been stolen and brought to Constantinople by the Byzantine general Giorgio Maniace as war booty and where they remained for 86 years. From 3 to 5 February, more than a million faithful and tourists arrive in Catania.</string>
    <string name="desc_etna">The Etna (Mungibeddu or Muntagna in Sicilian) is a Sicilian volcanic complex originating in the Quaternary and is the highest terrestrial active volcano of the Eurasian Plaque. Its frequent eruptions throughout history have changed, sometimes even profoundly, the surrounding landscape, repeatedly coming to threaten the populations that have settled around it over the millennia. On June 21, 2013, the XXXVII session of the UNESCO Committee, which met in Phnom Penh in Cambodia, included Mount Etna in the list of assets that constitute the Heritage of Humanity.</string>
    <string name="desc_acitrezza">Aci Trezza (Trizza in Sicilian) is a fraction of the municipality of Aci Castello, in the metropolitan city of Catania. Fishing center of ancient and remarkable tradition, is famous for its landscape. It overlooks the Ionian Sea and is about 9 kilometers from Catania. It is the country where ice cream was invented, thanks to the work of the chef Francesco Procopio dei Coltelli.</string>
    <string name="desc_duomo">The metropolitan cathedral of Sant \\ \'Agata is the main Catholic place of worship in Catania, the mother church of the homonymous metropolitan archdiocese and seat of the homonymous parish.     The cathedral is dedicated to the virgin and martyr Sant \\ \'Agata, patron saint of the city of Catania and is located in the historic center of the city in the south-east side of Piazza del Duomo, in the Duomo district of Catania or Terme Achilliane - Piano di San Filippo.     In July 1926 he was elevated to the dignity of minor basilica by Pope Pius XI.</string>
    <string name="duomo">Duomo</string>
    <string name="desc_catania">Catania is an Italian town of 315 589 inhabitants, the capital of the homonymous metropolitan city in Sicily and the heart of an urban area of ​​about 700 000 residents extended to the south eastern slopes of Mount Etna.  It is the center of the most densely populated metropolitan area of ​​Sicily, and a larger conurbation known as the linear system of eastern Sicily, which has about 1,700,000 inhabitants on an area of ​​2,400 square kilometers. The city is also the economic and infrastructural fulcrum of the District of South-East Sicily, established on February 26, 2014 in the presence of the then president of the Italian Republic Giorgio Napolitano. It is the most populated municipality in Italy that is not the regional capital.  Founded in 729 BC from the Calcidesi of nearby Naxos, the city boasts an ancient history characterized by various dominations whose remains enrich its artistic, architectural and cultural heritage.  Under the Aragonese dynasty it was the capital of the Kingdom of Sicily, and since 1434 by the will of King Alfonso V it is home to the oldest University of the island.  In the course of its history it has been repeatedly affected by volcanic eruptions (the most imposing, in historical times, is that of 1669) and by earthquakes (the most catastrophic ones remembered were those of 1169 and 1693).  Catania has been a native or adoptive homeland of some of Italy\'s most famous artists and writers, including the composers Vincenzo Bellini and Giovanni Pacini and the writers Giovanni Verga, Luigi Capuana, Federico De Roberto and Nino Martoglio.  The baroque of its historic center has been declared a UNESCO World Heritage Site, along with that of seven towns in the Val di Noto (Caltagirone, Militello in the Val di Catania, Modica, Noto, Palazzolo Acreide, Ragusa and Scicli), in 2002 .  The main industrial, logistical and commercial center of Sicily, is the seat of the Vincenzo Bellini Airport, the largest in Southern Italy.</string>
</resources>